（上条(かみじょう)）
わたくしこと 上条当麻(とうま)は―
I, Kamijyo Touma,
came in contact with a homeless shrine maiden, who, *quote* calls herself a magician *end quote*.
行き倒れの巫女(みこ)さん
（自称 魔法使い）
…と出会ってしまう
ステイルとかいう
魔術師と一緒に―
Together with another magician called Stiyl, I headed to where this shrine maiden was being held captive...
巫女さんが監禁されてる
ヤバイとこに向かった俺が―
そこで見たものは…
...and what I saw there was...
This is just a corpse.
（ｽﾃｲﾙ）
これは ただの死体だよ
～♪
#08 Ars Magna
The Alchemy of God
A corpse?!
（上条）
死体？
He's probably from the Thirteen Knights of the Roman Catholic Church.
（ｽﾃｲﾙ）
恐らく ローマ正教の
十三騎士団だろう
この様子じゃ 全滅みたいだね
From the looks of this, they were probably completely annihilated.
Why?
（上条）どうして？
（ｽﾃｲﾙ）ここは戦場だ
We're on a battlefield.
What's so surprising about a corpse or two lying around?
死体の１つ２つ転がっていたって
何の不思議がある？
Why isn't anyone shocked or panicking?
（上条）
なんで誰も騒ぎ立てないんだ？
（学生）
フフッ… メグミ お疲れ
Megumi, long day, huh?
What was that just now?
（上条）
何だ？ 今の
The difference between the "outerside" and the "innerside".
（ｽﾃｲﾙ）表と裏だね ここは
（上条）はぁ？
These students are inhabitants of the outerside of the coin;
コインの表の
住人である生徒たちは…
コインの裏の住人 僕たち外敵に
気づくことができない
they won't be able to notice us enemies from outside that are on the innerside of the coin right now.
僕たちも 彼らに
一切 干渉することはできない
Neither can we, in any way, interfere with their actions.
Don't even try it.
（ｽﾃｲﾙ）
ムダだよ
Without destroying the core of the magic, you won't be able to dispel this seal.
魔術の核をつぶさないかぎり
この結界を破ることはできない
核そのものは 結界の外に
置いてあるんだろうけどね
I'm sure the core is somewhere outside, though.
Looks like I have one more reason to fight now.
戦う理由が増えたみたいだ
Hey, couldn't we have taken the elevator?
なあ エレベーターに乗ってっても
よかったんじゃねえか？
コインの裏にいる僕たちに―
We're on the innerside of the coin,
コインの表にあるボタンを
押すことはできない
so we won't be able to press buttons that are on the outerside of the coin.
ふ～ん…
じゃ 電話は どうなるんだろう
So, what about phones?
（ｽﾃｲﾙ）はぁ？
（上条）あ～ いや
Huh?
Ah, you know, I was wondering if I could call from the innerside of the coin to the outerside of the coin.
コインの裏から電話して
コインの表に通じるのかなと
フッ… 試してみればいい
See for yourself, then.
うん　そうする
（プッシュ音）
I'll do that.
Ah, th-this is Index Libro-
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）
はい！　こちら あの…
インデックス･ライブロ …じゃない
上条です あの… はい
I mean, this is Kamijyo speaking!
Um, yes.
What, is this the first time you've answered a phone?
お前…
電話に出るのって初めてか？
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）
はい！
Ahhh-
…て あれ？　この声 当麻だ
Ah, this is Touma's voice.
And Touma, for you to be using something as exaggerated, excessive, cumbersome,
当麻　わざわざ電話なんて―
大げさで
仰々しく 面倒くさくて―
心臓に悪い物なんか使って
どうしたの？
and unfriendly as a phone, what's wrong?
No, nothing.
あ～ いや 別に
Ah, there were two lasagnas in the refrigerator,
あっ 冷蔵庫の中に ラザニアが
２つあったけど もしかして…
was that-
食ったんかい！
Did you eat them?!
アア…
冷蔵庫の中にプリンがあったけど
Ah, there was pudding in the refrigerator-
...What... Did you...
（上条）
なに？　まさか…
...Did you eat it?!
食ったんかい！
You ate it, didn't you?!
（上条）
食ったんだな？　食ったんだろう！
You ate it, right?!
Oh, well.
（上条）…て まあいい
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）えっ？
As long as I can reach you by phone.
とにかく
電話がつながるのならいいんだ
I'm hanging up.
（上条）切るぞ
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）えっ？
Ah, right, right.
I heard that your life is shortened a day for every minute you speak on the phone.
電話って １分話すと
１日 寿命が減るらしいぞ
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）ウワ～ッ！
（電話の切れる音）
Wh-What?
な… 何だよ？
Nothing.
別に
ただ少し緊張感に欠けると思ってね
I just thought you might be too relaxed.
I said we were on a battlefield,
yet you're chatting nonchalantly with a girl.
ここは戦場だというのに のんきに
女の子なんかと会話しちゃって
It's like, I don't care if you die because of your conceitedness,
その慢心が 己の身を滅ぼすなら
かまわないというか
and in fact, I'd be jumping for joy,
僕としては万々歳だけど
but heck, just don't drag me down because that's problematic.
（ｽﾃｲﾙ）
こっちの足まで
引っ張ってもらっちゃ困る
You jealous?
（上条）妬(や)いてるの？
（ｽﾃｲﾙ）ンッ…
Don't get it wrong.
間違うなよ　恋愛対象として
あの子を見ているわけではない
She's not a target of romance.
（ｽﾃｲﾙ）君だって知ってるだろう
（上条）あっ…
You should be well aware of that.
Until now, her body was one that would die unless her memories were erased in one year periods.
（ｽﾃｲﾙ）
あの子は 今まで―
１年周期で 全ての記憶を消さねば
生きていけない体だった
（ｽﾃｲﾙ）
今 君のいる位置には
かつて さまざまな人がいた
Many people were in the position you're in right now.
父親や きょうだいや 親友や先生
To become her father, her sibling, her friend, her teacher...
Many people wished to become different roles for her.
皆 さまざまなものに
なろうとしたんだ
You have succeeded in what I failed to do in the past.
かつて 僕は失敗し
そして 君は成功した
（ｽﾃｲﾙ）
それだけさ
That's all.
That's the only difference between you and me.
僕らの違いは たった それだけだよ
That's right.
（上条）
そうだ　インデックスを助けたのは
今の俺じゃない
The one that saved Index isn't me, right now.
The one that Index desires is...
インデックスが求めているのは―
...me, before I lost my memories...
記憶を失う前の俺なんだ
And that was so mean!
（学生）それで ひどいのよ
（学生）ホントに？
Yeah, for real.
（ｽﾃｲﾙ）
ふ～ん…
科学宗教ってのは初めてだけど
This is the first time I've seen the science religion,
but this seems pretty normal.
至って 普通だね
I'd think they have a portrait of the religion's founder framed somewhere.
てっきり 教祖さまの顔写真でも
飾ってあるのかと思ったよ
It does seem pretty safe...
確かに 危険度は低そうだけど
（ｽﾃｲﾙ）マズイかな
（上条）うん？　えっ？
Shit...
（ｽﾃｲﾙ）
呆(ほう)けるなよ
Don't be stupid,
because there's no way people on the outerside of the coin can see people like us on the innerside of the coin.
コインの表の住人に―
コインの裏の僕らが
見えるはずがない
The wings of the seraph shine brightly.
（学生１）
熾天(してん)の翼は輝く光
The bright light is a pure white color that reveals sins.
（学生２）
輝く光は罪を暴く純白
The pure white color is the mark of purity.
（学生たち）
純白は浄化の証し
The mark is the result of one's actions.
証しは行動の結果
結果は未来　未来は時間
One's actions represent the future.
The future is time.
Time is uniform.
（ｽﾃｲﾙ）自動の警報か
（上条）はぁ？
Auto-warning, eh?
Uniformity is all.
本来 コインの表にいるはずの
生徒たちを―
These students that were supposed to be on the outerside of the coin...
All is created by the past.
The past is the cause.
...have been put on the innerside of the coin.
コインの裏に立たせているんだろう
There is but one cause.
One is sin.
（生徒たち）
ひとつは罪　罪は人
Sins are humans.
人は罪を恐れ 恐れるは罪悪
Humans fear, and fear is guilt.
罪悪とは己の中に
Guilt rests within oneself.
If there is something one despises within,
己の中に
忌み嫌うべきものがあるならば
the wings of the seraph will reveal your sins,
熾天の翼により 己の罪を暴き
内から はじけ飛ぶべし
and force it from within you.
Okay, Imagine Breaker.
（ｽﾃｲﾙ）ほ～ら 幻想殺し(イマジンブレイカー)
（上条）うん？
You're up!
（ｽﾃｲﾙ）君の出番だ！
（上条）お… おい！
H-Hey!
（立ち上がる音）
…たく
Geez...
（上条）ハァハァ…
（ｽﾃｲﾙ）おい 逃げるな！
Hey, don't run away!
Your right hand was able
to fend off a Dragon Breath attack!
その右手は “竜王の殺息(ドラゴンブレス)”の
一撃も防いだんだぞ
So you must be nuts to be showing your back right now!
なのに 無防備な背中を
見せるだなんて どうかしてるぞ
I don't want to hear that from someone using me as a shield!
（上条）
人を盾にしといて よく言うぜ
量が絶望的だ　あんなもん
右手ひとつで対処できるか！
There's just too many of them!
One right hand won't be able to cover them all!
But, damn!
（ｽﾃｲﾙ）
しかし レプリカとはいえ―
That may be a replica, but to be able to reproduce Gregorio's Choir...
グレゴリオの聖歌隊を
作り出すなんて
（上条）
何だよ？
そのグレゴリオの何とかってのは
What's that Gregorio whatever?!
（ｽﾃｲﾙ）
本来は 3,333人の修道士を
聖堂に配し―
Originally, it was a grand magic spell that employed 3,333 monks in a cathedral and gathered their prayers.
その祈りを集める大魔術だ
ハン！ そんなもん まともにやって
勝てるはずねえじゃねえか
Then, there's no way we can beat that head on!
No, Gregorio's Choir requires the simultaneous control of a large amount of people or else it won't work.
いいや　グレゴリオの聖歌隊は―
大勢の人間を
同時に操らなければ成功しない
If we can destroy whatever's synchronizing them...
そのシンクロのカギとなるものを
破壊すれば…
Now, I do have a secret plan.
（ｽﾃｲﾙ）
ひとつ秘策があると言えば
あるんだけど
Then use it already!
（上条）あるなら さっさと使え！
（ｽﾃｲﾙ）そうかい？
Oh yeah?
ウワッ！　とっとっと…
ンッ… 何すんだ てめえ！
What the hell are you doing?!
Bad luck, scarecrow.
バッドラック スケアクロウ
The flame punishes sins.
（少女）
罪を罰するは炎
Purgatory governs the flames.
炎をつかさどるは煉獄(れんごく)
Purgatory was created to burn sinners,
煉獄は 罪人を焼くために作られし
神が認める唯一の暴力
as the only violence God recognizes.
Violence is the acknowledgment of death.
（少女）暴力は死の肯定
（切れる音）
Acknowledgement is recognition.
肯定は認識
Stop it!
やめろ！　自分の体が―
Recognition rests within you.
Don't you see that your own body is in trouble?!
ヤバくなってることぐらい
分かってんだろう！
Within refers to the world.
Connect your inner self with the outside world.
自己の内面と世界の外面をつなげ…
ウワッ！
What the...
な… 何だ？
What is this...
これは 一体…
それにしても
あの錬金術師も ゆがんだものだ
But man...
That alchemist is messed up...
The one cutting a path through enemies should be oneself, not others...
血路とは 他人ではなく
己を切り開いて作るものだろうに
（ｱｳﾚｵﾙｽ）自然…
（ｽﾃｲﾙ）うん？
Naturally, using Gregorio Replica would definitely direct you to the core no matter where it was hidden.
（ｱｳﾚｵﾙｽ）
“偽･聖歌隊(グレゴリオ＝レプリカ)”を使えば―
どこに潜んでいようが―
核のもとまで
おびき出せるとは思っていた
当然 侵入者は２人だったはずだが
Inevitably, there were two intruders to begin with, but...
Evidently, your familiar has been devoured by Gregorio Replica?
現然 貴様の使い魔は
偽･聖歌隊(グレゴリオ＝レプリカ)に のまれたか
フッ… あいにく
あれは 想像以上に しぶといんでね
Unfortunately for you, that one's much tougher than you think.
それで 僕を招き寄せるとは
どういうつもりなんだ？
And?
What do you intend on doing by luring me here?
錬金術師 アウレオルス＝イザード
Alchemist, Aureolus Izzard.
（姫神(ひめがみ)）
手当てすれば平気
Treatment suffices.
But...
（上条）
けど…
Her skin was torn open and her capillaries injured.
（姫神）
皮膚を剥がされて
毛細血管が傷ついてるだけ
Had her arteries been cut, it would be worse.
動脈を切られたら
これでは済まない
お前 医者でもないのに…
You're not a doctor, and...
I am much more informed about
the flow of blood than other people.
（姫神）
血の流れについてなら
私は人より詳しい
Assist me.
（姫神）手伝って
（上条）あっ…
（上条）うわ ちょ…
（姫神）うろたえない
Ah, wai-
Do not panic.
That is rude to the victim.
（姫神）ケガ人に失礼
（上条）あっ…
ねえ スフィンクス
当麻は どこに行ったんだろう？
Hey, Sphinx.
Where did Touma go?
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）
冷蔵庫の中にプリンがあったけど
Ah, there was pudding in the refrigerator-
（上条）
なに？　まさか…
...What... Did you...
...Did you eat it?!
（上条）
食ったんかい！　食ったんだな？
食ったんだろう！
You ate it, didn't you?!
You ate it, right?!
（上条）…て まあいい
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）えっ？
Oh, well.
なんか変　当麻が
プリンを勝手に食べられて―
Something's weird.
There's no way Touma would just say
"oh, well" when someone eats his pudding.
“まあいい”で
済ませるはずはないんだよ
ルーンの刻印！
Rune marks!
Done for now.
とりあえず おしまい
（上条）
…てか お前 すげえ腕だな
You're... pretty skilled...
Are you a certain famous doctor without a license?
（上条）
もしかして
無免許の名医さん …とか？
（姫神）医者じゃない
（上条）えっ？　それじゃ…
Not a doctor.
But then...
私 魔法使い
I'm a magician.
えっと… どの辺が魔法使い？
Umm, which part shows that you're a magician?
（姫神）それなら持ってる
（上条）えっ？
I have this.
（姫神）これ
（上条）うん？
This.
魔法のステッキ
A magic wand.
（上条）
…て 警棒じゃねえか！
That's just a police club!
（姫神）新素材
（上条）ふざけんな！
New material.
Quit joking!
あっ 救急車 呼ばねえと
We need to call an ambulance.
（姫神）
それはいい
Good idea.
Don't sound as if you're not a part of this.
（上条）
人ごとみたいに言ってんじゃねえよ
お前だって帰るんだから
You need to go home, too.
だから
こんなとこに閉じ込められてねえで
That is, stop being held here, so that we can go out.
外に出ようぜ
私にも目的がある
I have my own objective.
ここから抜け出すことではなく
ここでなければ できない目的
An objective that does not involve escaping from here,
but to achieve something that I can only accomplish while here.
違う…
No.
“錬金術師がいなければ
不可能な目的”と言うのが正解
It's more accurate to say that without the alchemist, the objective would be impossible.
（上条）
けど 仲間だったら 監禁して
立てこもったりしねえだろう
But, a friend wouldn't hold someone, okay?
（姫神）
それは
アウレオルスに乗っ取られる前
That was before Aureolus took over.
私が外へ出ないのは
必要性を感じないだけ
I do not sense the necessity of going out.
Going out without caution will just attract "that".
不用意に出れば
あれを呼び寄せるから
じゃ お前 “吸血鬼”ってのに
気づかれたくないから―
Then, you're saying you've been hiding here all this time just because you don't want to be noticed by vampires.
こんな所に
ずっと隠れてるっていうのか？
Vampires.
吸血鬼…
どんな生き物か知ってる？
Do you know what kind of an organism they're like?
Nothing is different.
（姫神）変わらない
（上条）あっ…
私たちと何も変わらない
Nothing is different between them and us.
They can laugh, and act for the sake of others.
（姫神）
誰かのために笑い 行動できる
そんな人たち
That's what they are.
My blood attracts them with its nice smell.
私の血は 甘い匂いで
そんな人たちを招き寄せる
I attract them, gather them, and kill them.
招き 集め 殺す
理由はない
There is no motive.
I just kill them without exception.
ただ一度の例外もなく
殺し尽くしてしまう
（姫神）
学園都市は 力を扱う場所だから
その秘密も分かると思ってた
Academy City is a place that governs power,
so I thought they would know the secret behind this.
秘密が分かれば
取り除く方法もあると
If the secret is known, then the method to remove it might be available...
だけど
そんなものは どこにもなかった
But the secret isn't known.
I don't want to kill anymore.
私は もう殺したくない
I have decided that if I had to kill anyone, I would kill myself.
誰かを殺すぐらいなら 私は
自分を殺してみせると決めたから
ひとつ 聞かせてくれ
Let me ask you one thing.
If you don't want to attract vampires,
吸血鬼を呼びたくないってんなら
then why were you spending all your money on food outside?
なんで
外で食い倒れたりしてたんだ？
Simple.
（姫神）
簡単
アウレオルスが私を必要とするのは
吸血鬼が欲しいから
Aureolus needs me because he wants a vampire sample.
If I stay inside the seal, then I can't attract vampires.
私が結界の内にいては
吸血鬼を招くことはできない
But...
けど それじゃ
お前の目的と正反対じゃねえか
Isn't that the opposite of your objective?
Aureolus promised me...
アウレオルスは約束した
“吸血鬼を絶対 傷つけない”って
...that he wouldn't hurt the vampire.
Aureolus said...
アウレオルスは言った
“助けたい人がいる”って
...that there's someone he wants to save...
“吸血鬼の力が必要だ”って
...that he needed the powers of a vampire.
That's why the pact was made.
だから 約束した
To use this power not to kill,
“殺すためでなく 助けるために
この力を使う”って
but to save.
そんなのダメだ
That's wrong.
もし そいつが
お前の言うとおりの人間だとしたら
If he really were the kind of person you speak of,
then I couldn't let him commit any more wrongs.
これ以上
間違えさせることなんてできない
このまま進ませちまったら―
If I let this happen, then it'll really end up being an irreversible mistake.
本当に 取り返しのつかないことに
なっちまう
（ｱｳﾚｵﾙｽ）
必然… 私のどこが
取り返しがつかないと語るか？
Necessarily, what about me leads you to say that this will be irreversible?
He's...
あいつが…
寛然　子細ない
すぐ そちらへ向かおう
Composedly, it does not matter.
I shall come for you right away.
ウワッ！
Naturally, you have questions I need not answer.
当然　疑問は湧いて出るだろうが
答える義務なし
ンッ… てめえ！
You...
You shall not approach me any further.
これ以上 貴様は こちらへ来るな
ンッ… この！
You...
な… なんで？
H-How come...
Disappointingly, you bore me, young man.
憮然(ぶぜん)　つまらんな 少年
（ｱｳﾚｵﾙｽ）吹き飛べ！
（姫神）待って！
Fade away-
Wait!
バ… バカ野郎！
Y-You idiot!
“吸血殺し(ディープブラッド)”は
吸血鬼を殺せるほどの力
Deep Blood has enough power to kill vampires.
なら…
That means...
And so at the very end, you ended up leaning on Deep Blood, relying on it, and prayed.
結局 最後の最後に 貴様は
吸血殺し(ディープブラッド)にすがり 頼り 願った
そこに 私と何の違いがある？
What's the difference between you and me, then?
That's not true!
（姫神）
そんなことはない
This person doesn't know the significance of Deep Blood.
この人は
“吸血殺し(ディープブラッド)”の意味を知らなかった
ここまで来たのは―
He came here to rescue someone that he met today and barely knows.
今日 顔を合わせただけの他人を
助けるため
Aureolus Izzard, what is your objective?
アウレオルス＝イザード
あなたの目的は なに？
Is satisfying yourself by killing civilians your objective?
（姫神）
ただの一般人を殺して
満足することが あなたの目的？
そんな つまらないことが
目的だというなら 私は もう降りる
If that kind of meaningless act is your objective,
then I shall quit.
I have the right of choosing to bite
my own tongue to end my own life.
私にも 舌をかみ
自らの命を絶つ選択権はある
必然
こんな所へ時間を割く余裕もなし
Necessarily, there is no time to waste in a place like this.
少年 案ずるな　殺しはしない
Young man, do not worry.
I won't kill you.
Forget everything that happened here!
ここで起きたことは 全て忘れろ
（インデックス）
むっ… ここか
Here, huh?
Where the mana that was being supplied to
the runes near Touma's room is completely cut off.
当麻の部屋のルーンに
送られてる魔力が―
プッツリ途切れてる
Where am I?
ここは…
君がいるということは―
That you're here means we're still in Japan.
日本には違いないだろう
何か重要なことを
忘れているような…
I think I'm forgetting something important...
...am I right?
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）違うかい？
（上条）うん
（ｽﾃｲﾙ）
フゥ…
Well, it's probably something that doesn't need to be remembered.
まあ 思い出す必要もない程度の
ことなんだろうさ
（上条）
う～ん… そうなのか？
You sure?
（ｱｳﾚｵﾙｽ）
全て忘れろ
Forget everything that happened here!
Let me teach you a charm that will erase your doubts.
（上条）
お前の疑問を―
さっくり解消させる おまじないを
教えてやる
うん？　東洋のまじないは
神裂(かんざき)の専門なんだ　彼女に聞くよ
Oriental charms are Kanzaki's specialty.
I'll ask her.
Just close your eyes and put your tongue out.
いいから　目をつむって 舌を出せ
ベ～ッて
Here's a souvenir for having the balls to use me as a bait and escaping yourself!
“よくも 人さまを囮(おとり)に使って
逃げ延びやがったな”記念
There's a seal set up to prevent enemy intruders from escaping.
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）
内に入り込んだ敵を
逃がさないための―
結界が張られている
Hmm, it has been a while.
（ｱｳﾚｵﾙｽ）ふむ… 久しいな
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）あっ…
Who are you?
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）誰？
（ｱｳﾚｵﾙｽ）覚えておらんか
You don't remember me?
必然　アウレオルス＝イザードと
いう名にも聞き覚えはあるまい
Naturally, you wouldn't happen to recall the name, Aureolus Izzard?
No, perhaps that should be a fortunate occurrence.
否　それでこそ
僥倖(ぎょうこう)と呼ばねばならんが
Sleep.
（ｱｳﾚｵﾙｽ）眠れ
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）アア…
（上条）
おい　あいつら 入り口にいた…
Hey, these guys were the ones at the entrance-
The remnants of the Thirteen Knights, huh?
（ｽﾃｲﾙ）十三騎士団の生き残りか
（上条）あっ…
Commence attack!
（騎士）
攻撃を開始する！
Gregorio Choir.
（ｽﾃｲﾙ）“真･聖歌隊(グレゴリオ＝クアイア)”
（上条）はぁ？
The true choir of Gregorio.
正真正銘のグレゴリオの聖歌隊だよ
But, didn't you say a lot of people were required for this Gregorio whatever?
（上条）
けど お前 グレゴリオの何とかには
大人数が必要だって…
Those 3,333 monks are probably sending their prayers right now from St. Peter's Basilica.
（ｽﾃｲﾙ）
今ごろ バチカン大聖堂では―
3,333人の信徒が
祈りをささげているんだろうさ
Revelation 8:7 -
（騎士）
ヨハネ黙示録 第８章
第７節より抜粋
"When the first angel blew his trumpet, hail and fire were mixed with blood and thrown to the earth"
第１の御使(みつか)い その手に持つ
滅びの管楽器の音をここに再現せよ
（上条）
あいつら 何する気だ？
What the hell are they trying to do?
Holy magic bombardment.
（ｽﾃｲﾙ）聖呪爆撃
（上条）爆撃？
Bombardment?
Himegami and other students are still inside!
あの中には姫神が…
無関係の生徒たちだって
（爆発音）
（ｽﾃｲﾙ･上条）ウワッ！
（ｽﾃｲﾙ）
崩れるぞ！
It's gonna collapse!
（上条）
巻き戻ってる？
It's rising again?
（ｽﾃｲﾙ）
“黄金練成(アルス＝マグナ)”
Ars Magna.
（上条）
“黄金練成(アルス＝マグナ)”？
Ars Magna?
あれが 僕らの敵 アウレオルスの
本当の実力
That is our enemy's,
Aureolus Izzard's true power.
Sphinx?!
スフィンクス？
まさか… これ インデックスの…
Don't tell me...
...this is Index's...
～♪
Next Episode
The varied clashes surrounding Index.
（上条）
インデックスを巡って
交錯する さまざまな確執
The moment the alchemist who rebels against destiny shows his fangs,
運命にあらがう錬金術師が
牙をむいた そのとき
roars will resonate inside the Misawa Cram School.
三沢塾(みさわじゅく)に咆哮(ほうこう)が響く
次回 「吸血殺し(ディープブラッド)」
Next time, "Deep Blood".
When science and magic cross paths,
科学と魔術が交差するとき
物語は始まる
this epic will begin!